You know the legend. Now meet the man.
Bruce Lee: A Warrior's Journey is a documentary,
action film directed by John Little.
Documentary on the legendary martial artist Bruce Lee, with a focus on
the production of his unfinished film Game of Death.
Using interviews and behind-the-scenes footage, Lee aficionado John Little paints a portrait of the world's most famous action hero,
concluding with a new cut of Game of Death's action finale, reconstructed from Lee's notes and recently-recovered footage.
Self (archival), played by Bruce Lee.
Narrator (voice), played by Doug Copsey.
Self, played by Linda Lee Cadwell.
Self, played by Kareem Abdul-Jabbar.
Self, played by Taky Kimura.
Self, played by Ji Han-Jae.
Bruce Lee: A Warrior's Journey (Chinese: 李小龍：死亡遊戲之旅) is a 2000 documentary
film about the martial artist Bruce Lee and Jeet Kune Do.
The documentary includes never-before-seen behind-the-scenes footage of Bruce Lee's life, as well as parts of
the original footage of his incomplete film Game of Death, which had been left out of the film.
The film explores themes of martial arts, philosophy,
interview, behind the scenes, east asian lead.